<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Rami Dahhan</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Rami Dahhan</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 12:13:38 +0530</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Data Literacy for Product Management: Causal models and variations.</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/post1/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 12:13:38 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/post1/</guid>
      <description>How many controllable inputs do you know about your product right now? Something like “10% increase in detail page views where the products were in stock and immediately ready for two-day shipping directly improves conversation rates by 1%” - Example from Amazon usecase.&#xA;If the answer is none, this article is for you.&#xA;Why become Data-Driven? Data embodies knowledge, and from this knowledge, you can construct a causal model of your product or business.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PM Perspectives: Org Structure and Daily Challenges</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/post2/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Jan 2024 12:13:38 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/post2/</guid>
      <description>Why does org structure matter to a Product Manager? Exploring the significance of organizational structure for Product Managers leads us to a fascinating concept known as Conway&amp;rsquo;s Law. In 1967, Melvin E. Conway introduced a groundbreaking idea: the systems we develop often mirror our company&amp;rsquo;s communication patterns. This means if your organization operates in isolated silos, it&amp;rsquo;s likely that your products will reflect those divisions.&#xA;Why now? &amp;ldquo;Efficiency Reloaded&amp;rdquo; is the buzz for 2024.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
