<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Rami Dahhan</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Rami Dahhan</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 12:13:38 +0530</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Data Literacy for Product Management: Causal models and variations.</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/post1/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 12:13:38 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/post1/</guid>
      <description>How many controllable inputs do you know about your product right now? Something like “10% increase in detail page views where the products were in stock and immediately ready for two-day shipping directly improves conversation rates by 1%” - Example from Amazon usecase.&#xA;If the answer is none, this article is for you.&#xA;Why become Data-Driven? Data embodies knowledge, and from this knowledge, you can construct a causal model of your product or business.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>About Me</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/about/</guid>
      <description>Welcome! I&amp;rsquo;m Rami Dahhan, a Technical Product Manager with a passion for leveraging data-driven insights to craft long-term product roadmaps. With over a decade of experience at leading corporations like Starbucks, Rogers, and Bell, I specialize in aligning product development with strategic business goals, ensuring every feature we introduce is user-centric and backed by solid data.&#xA;My academic background, with a Bachelor&amp;rsquo;s in Computer Engineering and a Master&amp;rsquo;s in Technology Innovation Management, laid the foundation for my approach to product management: rigorous, analytical, and always forward-looking.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PM Perspectives: Org Structure and Daily Challenges</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/post2/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Jan 2024 12:13:38 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/post2/</guid>
      <description>Why does org structure matter to a Product Manager? To understand why organizational structure matters so much for Product Managers, let&amp;rsquo;s dive into Conway&amp;rsquo;s Law. Imagine this: in 1967, Melvin E. Conway introduced the groundbreaking concept that the systems we develop often mirror our company&amp;rsquo;s communication structures. This implies that if your organization is siloed, it&amp;rsquo;s likely your products will reflect those silos.&#xA;For Product Managers, deciphering your organization&amp;rsquo;s structure is akin to discovering the secret ingredient that enables the creation of outstanding products that are not only successful but also strategically aligned.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
